<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
    <channel>
        <title>Search for JavaScript</title>
        <link>https://azu.github.io/book-rss/JavaScript.xml</link>
        <description>Search for JavaScript</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Tue, 12 Jan 2021 14:16:09 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>book-rss</generator>
        <copyright>book-rss</copyright>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[JavaScript for Beginners]]></title>
            <link>http://books.google.com/books?id=WqQNzgEACAAJ&amp;dq=JavaScript&amp;hl=&amp;cd=1&amp;source=gbs_api</link>
            <guid>http://books.google.com/books?id=WqQNzgEACAAJ&amp;dq=JavaScript&amp;hl=&amp;cd=1&amp;source=gbs_api</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 17 Nov 2020 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Is it a great idea to try to use JavaScript for computer programming? How would you use it? JavaScript is among the widely computer programming languages in the world. It has been in the computer programming field for well over 40 years, and it is known as a high level language due to the competence it has established in the programming field. JavaScript is used by various software companies in the world, so much that many computer operations will not work without it. So, it's a great idea to try using it too. The most exciting feature of JavaScript is that it allows you to program using English-based commands, not numeric codes and that makes it a whole lot easier for humans to program. This means programmers can read and easily understand the computer language. Another uniqueness of JavaScript is that the producing company always update the language so that modern operations and newly developed patterns can be easily programmed into a computer. That sounds great, and that is a reason you should trust JavaScript. But that certainly comes with a load of problems. It makes it all the more complicated for you to try using JavaScript. The first is that there are vital skills you need in order to navigate JavaScript as an expert. If you are a beginner who hasn't even run the JavaScript application by accident or you have some raw idea, the book attached below can help you explore easily. It will provide details of data structure, basic programming structure, advance programming structure, various kinds of test execution and so many others. It is also written in a simple and relative style that would answer every question you have at every turn of practice. This book is ideal for you as a starter who knows nothing about programming. Step by step, you will find all the basics of computer coding with JavaScript. So, be sure reading this means you are training to become a top class programmer who can confidently code computers with a sound knowledge of JavaScript Basics. Among others, you will learn: - What is JavaScript? (JavaScript in XHTML documents, in browsers, etc.) - Why JavaScript? (Types of JavaScript execution, how to create one, Python Vs Java and so on) - Basic Programming Structure - Advance Programming Structure - Data Structures: Objects and Arrays. - Higher Order Functions - What is JavaScript Cookies? Be rest assured, every piece of information you'd like to find is attached in one of these chapters. Whether your research is for personal, or official reasons, this book can give you all the basic you need to know about JavaScript.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[It is also written in a simple and relative style that would answer every question you have at every turn of practice. This book is ideal for you as a starter who knows nothing about programming.]]></content:encoded>
            <enclosure url="http://books.google.com/books/content?id=WqQNzgEACAAJ&printsec=frontcover&img=1&zoom=1&source=gbs_api" length="0" type="image//books/content"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[JavaScript]]></title>
            <link>http://books.google.com/books?id=EJzuDwAAQBAJ&amp;printsec=frontcover&amp;dq=JavaScript&amp;hl=&amp;cd=2&amp;source=gbs_api</link>
            <guid>http://books.google.com/books?id=EJzuDwAAQBAJ&amp;printsec=frontcover&amp;dq=JavaScript&amp;hl=&amp;cd=2&amp;source=gbs_api</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jun 2020 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[All of JavaScript's newest features, in depth, made easy to understand. JavaScript is a rapidly changing language and it can be challenging to keep up with all the new toys being added. JavaScript: The New Toys explores the newest features of the world's most popular programming language while also showing readers how to track what's coming next. After setting the stage by covering who manages the process of improving JavaScript, how new features get introduced, terminology, and a high-level overview of new features, it details each new or updated item in depth, with example uses, possible pitfalls, and expert recommendations for updating old habits in light of new features. JavaScript: The New Toys: Covers all the additions to JavaScript in ES2015-ES2019 plus a preview of ES2020 (and beyond) Explores the latest syntax: nullish coalescing, optional chaining, let and const, class syntax, private methods, private fields, new.target, numeric separators, BigInt, destructuring, default parameters, arrow functions, async functions, await, generator functions, ... (rest and spread), template literals, binary and octal literals, ** (exponentiation), computed property/method names, for-of, for-await-of, shorthand properties, and others Details the new features and patterns including modules, promises, iteration, generators, Symbol, Proxy, reflection, typed arrays, Atomics, shared memory, WeakMap, WeakSet, and more Highlights common pitfalls and explains how to avoid them Shows how to follow the improvements process and even participate in the process yourself Explains how to use new features even before they're widely supported With its comprehensive coverage and friendly, accessible style, JavaScript: The New Toys provides an invaluable resource for programmers everywhere, whether they work in web development, Node.js, Electron, Windows Universal Apps, or another JavaScript environment.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[This book explores the newest features of the world&#39;s most popular programming language while also showing readers how to track what&#39;s coming next.]]></content:encoded>
            <enclosure url="http://books.google.com/books/content?id=EJzuDwAAQBAJ&printsec=frontcover&img=1&zoom=1&edge=curl&source=gbs_api" length="0" type="image//books/content"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[PHP MYSQL & JavaScript]]></title>
            <link>http://books.google.com/books?id=pj7BzQEACAAJ&amp;dq=JavaScript&amp;hl=&amp;cd=3&amp;source=gbs_api</link>
            <guid>http://books.google.com/books?id=pj7BzQEACAAJ&amp;dq=JavaScript&amp;hl=&amp;cd=3&amp;source=gbs_api</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Aug 2020 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[✓✓ PHP MYSQL & JavaScript ♥♥♥ ✓ Creating A Website With PHP ♥ What Is MYSQL And Does Your Business Need It ♥ Essential Tools In JavaScript ♥ ◆◆◆◆◆◆◆◆◆◆◆◆◆ ★ Creating a Website With PHP ★ PHP Web Development Beneficial For Online Business ★ Steps to Set Up MySQL Cluster For Multiple Dedicated Servers ★ What Is MySQL And Does Your Business Need It? ★ Essential Tools in JavaScript]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[✓✓ PHP MYSQL &amp; JavaScript ♥♥♥ ✓ Creating A Website With PHP ♥ What Is MYSQL And Does Your Business Need It ♥ Essential Tools In JavaScript ♥ ◆◆◆◆◆◆◆◆◆◆◆◆◆ ★ Creating a Website With PHP ★ PHP ...]]></content:encoded>
            <enclosure url="http://books.google.com/books/content?id=pj7BzQEACAAJ&printsec=frontcover&img=1&zoom=1&source=gbs_api" length="0" type="image//books/content"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[JavaScript Made Easy]]></title>
            <link>http://books.google.com/books?id=WubuBQAAQBAJ&amp;pg=PA44&amp;dq=JavaScript&amp;hl=&amp;cd=4&amp;source=gbs_api</link>
            <guid>http://books.google.com/books?id=WubuBQAAQBAJ&amp;pg=PA44&amp;dq=JavaScript&amp;hl=&amp;cd=4&amp;source=gbs_api</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jan 2021 14:16:09 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[JavaScript Made Easy covers the basics of JavaScript. It comprises many interesting sample scripts. The book was written in simple and plain English to help you master JavaScript easily . By reading this book, you should be able to use JavaScript in developing powerful and interactive websites.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<b>JavaScript</b>. Tutorial. Text with typewriter style : <b>JavaScript</b> Tutorial Subscript text: <br>
<b>JavaScript</b> Tutorial Superscript text:JavaScriptTutorial Strike-thru text: <br>
JavaScriptTutorial Red color text: <b>JavaScript</b> Tutorial Fontsize +3:&nbsp;...]]></content:encoded>
            <enclosure url="http://books.google.com/books/content?id=WubuBQAAQBAJ&printsec=frontcover&img=1&zoom=1&edge=curl&source=gbs_api" length="0" type="image//books/content"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[JavaScript Made Easy]]></title>
            <link>http://books.google.com/books?id=WubuBQAAQBAJ&amp;pg=PA52&amp;dq=JavaScript&amp;hl=&amp;cd=5&amp;source=gbs_api</link>
            <guid>http://books.google.com/books?id=WubuBQAAQBAJ&amp;pg=PA52&amp;dq=JavaScript&amp;hl=&amp;cd=5&amp;source=gbs_api</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jan 2021 14:16:09 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[JavaScript Made Easy covers the basics of JavaScript. It comprises many interesting sample scripts. The book was written in simple and plain English to help you master JavaScript easily . By reading this book, you should be able to use JavaScript in developing powerful and interactive websites.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[Example 9.2 &lt;html&gt; &lt;head&gt; &lt;title&gt;Example 9.2: <b>JavaScript</b> event-onmouseover&lt;<br>
/title&gt; &lt;/head&gt; &lt;body&gt; &lt;script language=&quot;<b>javascript</b>&quot;&gt; function mylink() {alert(&quot;<br>
Taking you to the web page now&quot;); location.href=&quot;http://<b>javascript</b>-tutor.net/&quot;; }&nbsp;...]]></content:encoded>
            <enclosure url="http://books.google.com/books/content?id=WubuBQAAQBAJ&printsec=frontcover&img=1&zoom=1&edge=curl&source=gbs_api" length="0" type="image//books/content"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Python Programming & Javascript]]></title>
            <link>http://books.google.com/books?id=4vrAzQEACAAJ&amp;dq=JavaScript&amp;hl=&amp;cd=6&amp;source=gbs_api</link>
            <guid>http://books.google.com/books?id=4vrAzQEACAAJ&amp;dq=JavaScript&amp;hl=&amp;cd=6&amp;source=gbs_api</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 17 Aug 2020 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[✓ Python Programming & Javascript ♥♥♥ ✓ What Is Javascript: Will Python Replace Java ♥♥ ✓ Enter Into The Programming World With Python Training ♥ ◆◆◆◆◆◆◆◆◆◆◆◆◆◆ ✓ Connecting Access To Python- ✓ Why Is Python Here To Stay? ✓ Enter Into The Programming World With Python Training- ✓ Will Python Replace Java? ✓ What Is JavaScript? ✓ Some Of The Differences Between JQuery And JavaScript- ✓ Best JavaScript Tutorial Guide for Beginners-]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[✓ Python Programming &amp; Javascript ♥♥♥ ✓ What Is Javascript: Will Python Replace Java ♥♥ ✓ Enter Into The Programming World With Python Training ♥ ◆◆◆◆◆◆◆◆◆◆◆◆◆◆ ✓ Connecting Access To Python- ...]]></content:encoded>
            <enclosure url="http://books.google.com/books/content?id=4vrAzQEACAAJ&printsec=frontcover&img=1&zoom=1&source=gbs_api" length="0" type="image//books/content"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[JavaScript]]></title>
            <link>http://books.google.com/books?id=fY2VzQEACAAJ&amp;dq=JavaScript&amp;hl=&amp;cd=7&amp;source=gbs_api</link>
            <guid>http://books.google.com/books?id=fY2VzQEACAAJ&amp;dq=JavaScript&amp;hl=&amp;cd=7&amp;source=gbs_api</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 30 May 2020 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[JavaScript has become the most popular programming language in the world. It has attained that position by being easy to use and powerful in its capabilities. It wasn't always that way but today it can be used to build virtually any application you desire. With the addition of HTML5 and CSS3, it allows for wonderfully animated and powerful web sites and applications without having to use other technologies such as Adobe Flash. JavaScript has also become much more standardized across the multiple browsers in use today. With the recent proliferation of libraries and frameworks that many developers use, the focus has shifted towards these new tools, but they still rely on native JavaScript. And these libraries and frameworks can greatly increase the size of your code as well as slowing down performance. This book covers best practices for coding in straight JavaScript as well as pointing out many areas for optimization. The goal is to help programmers produce smaller and faster JavaScript applications. Even programmers using frameworks and libraries can benefit from understanding the performance trade-offs they make when using those tools.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[This book covers best practices for coding in straight JavaScript as well as pointing out many areas for optimization. The goal is to help programmers produce smaller and faster JavaScript applications.]]></content:encoded>
            <enclosure url="http://books.google.com/books/content?id=fY2VzQEACAAJ&printsec=frontcover&img=1&zoom=1&source=gbs_api" length="0" type="image//books/content"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Programming JAVA: Java Programming, JavaScript, Coding: Programming Guide: LEARN IN A DAY!]]></title>
            <link>http://books.google.com/books?id=Crp_CwAAQBAJ&amp;printsec=frontcover&amp;dq=JavaScript&amp;hl=&amp;cd=9&amp;source=gbs_api</link>
            <guid>http://books.google.com/books?id=Crp_CwAAQBAJ&amp;printsec=frontcover&amp;dq=JavaScript&amp;hl=&amp;cd=9&amp;source=gbs_api</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jan 2016 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Discover the Easy Way to Learn Java and JavaScript! No matter how much time you spend on other subjects, there's no escaping the fact that you have to learn the basics of computer programming. It takes time and effort to learn a new programming language; however, once you know Java many doors will open for you! The good news is, there are short cuts you can take which cut down on the time and effort you must invest to master this skill. You'll find out the basics of Java, including Object Oriented Programming, Variable Declaration and Data Types, Control Statements, and Encapsulation. Also, find out the versatile uses of Boolean Objects, String Objects, andMath Objects in Java coding. Purchase Programming: Java, JavaScript Coding For Beginners - Learn In A Day NOW to learn Java the easy way! Stop wasting your money on expensive, time-consuming, and ineffective learning methods and start reaping the rewards of this highly-marketable skill! You'll be so glad you did!]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[Discover the Easy Way to Learn Java and JavaScript!]]></content:encoded>
            <enclosure url="http://books.google.com/books/content?id=Crp_CwAAQBAJ&printsec=frontcover&img=1&zoom=1&edge=curl&source=gbs_api" length="0" type="image//books/content"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Programming Online Tasks in Barebones JavaScript]]></title>
            <link>http://books.google.com/books?id=mgONzQEACAAJ&amp;dq=JavaScript&amp;hl=&amp;cd=10&amp;source=gbs_api</link>
            <guid>http://books.google.com/books?id=mgONzQEACAAJ&amp;dq=JavaScript&amp;hl=&amp;cd=10&amp;source=gbs_api</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 03 Apr 2020 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[This short but dense tutorial goes through programming an online psychological reaction time task, using only basic JavaScript. The idea is to provide the little technical tricks you need and some programming patterns I've found handy and easy to adjust to my own research. While there are lots of software packages out there, I like having the option not to have to rely on them.For most of the steps you'll only need a standard browser, but to complete it you'll really need to have hosting sorted out.This is a book-version for those who would like to have it; the tutorial is also available freely online.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[While there are lots of software packages out there, I like having the option not to have to rely on them.For most of the steps you&#39;ll only need a standard browser, but to complete it you&#39;ll really need to have hosting sorted out.This is a ...]]></content:encoded>
            <enclosure url="http://books.google.com/books/content?id=mgONzQEACAAJ&printsec=frontcover&img=1&zoom=1&source=gbs_api" length="0" type="image//books/content"/>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>